Register of the Ardashīr Zāhidī papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- Ambassador to the United States File, 1970-1979
  - Embassy files, 1970-1978
    - 1977 US House of Representatives correspondence, 1977-1978
      - R, 1977 (Box 82, Folder 30)
      - Rangel, Charles B., 1977 (Box 83, Folder 1)
      - Rhodes, John J., 1977 (Box 83, Folder 2)
      - Rogers, Paul, 1977 January-February (Box 83, Folder 3)
        Includes letters from Rebecca Rogers.
      - Ruppe, Philip E., 1977 (Box 83, Folder 4)
      - S, 1977 (Box 83, Folder 5)
      - Udall, Morris K., 1977 (Box 83, Folder 6)
      - W, 1977 (Box 83, Folder 7)
      - Wilson, Bob, 1976-1977 (Box 83, Folder 8)
      - Wright, Jim, 1977 (Box 83, Folder 9)
      - Yates, Sidney Richard, 1977 February-March (Box 83, Folder 10)
      - Zablocki, Clement John, 1977 (Box 83, Folder 11)
    - 1977 US governors correspondence (Box 83, Folder 12-13)
    - 1977 US mayors correspondence
      - Unfiled, 1977 (Box 83, Folder 14)
      - Beame, Abraham D., 1977 (Box 83, Folder 15)
      - Bradley, Tom, 1977 (Box 83, Folder 16)
      - Washington, Walter E., 1977 (Box 83, Folder 17)
    - 1977 education correspondence
      Includes correspondence with university presidents, professors, and staff.
      - Alaska Methodist University, 1977 (Box 83, Folder 18)
        Correspondence with Glenn A. Olds.
      - Pepperdine University, 1977 December (Box 83, Folder 19)
        Correspondence with M. Norvel Young.
      - Princeton University, 1977 (Box 83, Folder 20)
      - University of Utah, 1977 (Box 83, Folder 21)
      - Utah State University, 1976-1977 (Box 83, Folder 22)
        Includes correspondence with Daryl Chase.
    - 1977 business correspondence
      - Allis-Chalmers, 1977 (Box 84, Folder 1)
        Includes correspondence with Richard Augustus Edwards Jr. and David C. Scott.
      - Coyne, Marshall B., 1977 (Box 84, Folder 2)
      - Danzansky, Joseph B., 1977 (Box 84, Folder 3)
      - Fluor, J. Robert, 1977 (Box 84, Folder 4)
      - France, Bill, 1977 (Box 84, Folder 5)
      - Greenberg, Maurice R., 1977 (Box 84, Folder 6)
      - Hochstetter, Leo D., 1977 (Box 84, Folder 7)
        Includes copy of letter from George Weller to Leo D. Hochstetter.
      - Levitt, William, 1977 (Box 84, Folder 8)
        Includes copy of letter of intent between International Construction Co. Ltd. (Iran) and the Iranian Ministry of Housing and Urban Development.
      - Logan, John O., 1977 (Box 84, Folder 9)
      - McDonnell, Sanford N., 1977 (Box 84, Folder 10)
      - McMullen, John J., 1977 (Box 84, Folder 11)
      - Rockefeller, David, 1977 (Box 84, Folder 12)
    - 1977 organization correspondence, 1976-1977
      Correspondence with accompanying embassy documents.
      - Circus Saints and Sinners Club, 1977 (Box 84, Folder 13-15)
        Includes correspondence with Barnes Breeskin, accompanying organization fliers and publications, and photographs.
      - North Atlantic Treaty Organization, 1976-1977 (Box 84, Folder 16)
        Correspondence with Jospeh Luns and text from his farewell address for Henry Kissinger.
      - Organization of American States, 1977 (Box 84, Folder 17)
        Includes correspondence with Alejandro Orfila.
      - United Nations, 1976-1977 (Box 84, Folder 18)
      - United States Citizens' Congress, 1977 (Box 84, Folder 19)
        Correspondence with Barry Cooperstein and Baruch Korff.
      - Wolf Trap Foundation, 1977 (Box 85, Folder 1-2)
        Includes correspondence with Catherine Filene Shouse and foundation materials.
    - 1977 general correspondence, 1976-1977
      - A, 1977 (Box 85, Folder 3)
      - Acheson, David C., 1977 (Box 85, Folder 4)
      - Aga Khan, Sadruddin, Prince, 1977 (Box 85, Folder 5)
      - Alsop, Joseph, 1977 (Box 85, Folder 6)
      - Amesbury, Cecily and Walter R., 1977 (Box 85, Folder 7)
      - Anderson, Robert and Diane, 1977 (Box 85, Folder 8)
      - Anderson, Robert O., 1977 (Box 85, Folder 9)
      - B, 1977 (Box 85, Folder 10-11)
      - Bailey, Pearl, 1977 (Box 85, Folder 12-16)
        Includes accompanying photographs of Bailey from her trip to Jordan and with Gerald and Betty Ford.
      - Barnetson, William, 1977 (Box 85, Folder 17)
      - Becker, Ralph E., 1977 (Box 86, Folder 1)
      - Bjurstrom, Betty and Cecilia, 1977 (Box 86, Folder 2)
      - Braden, Joan and Thomas, 1977 (Box 86, Folder 3)
      - Bradley, Gene E., 1977 (Box 86, Folder 4)
      - Buchen, Philip W. and Bunny, 1977 (Box 86, Folder 5-6)
      - Bush, George, 1977 (Box 86, Folder 7)
      - Butz, Earl L., 1977 (Box 86, Folder 8)
      - C, 1977 (Box 86, Folder 9)
      - Catto, Henry E., 1977 (Box 86, Folder 10)
      - Cezayirli, Mehmet Faruk, 1977 March-April (Box 86, Folder 11)
        Includes Turkish clipping about royal family and typed interview with the Shah from Milliyet translated from Turkish into French.
      - Codus, William F., 1977 (Box 86, Folder 12)
      - Copley, Gregory R., 1976-1977 (Box 86, Folder 13)
      - Cullinane, Maurice J., 1977 (Box 86, Folder 14)
      - D, 1977 (Box 86, Folder 15)
      - Dahl, Arlene, 1977 (Box 86, Folder 16)
      - Douglas, Anne and Kirk, 1977 (Box 86, Folder 17)
      - Dudley, Henry A., 1977 (Box 87, Folder 1)
      - Duke, Angier Biddle and Robin, 1977 (Box 87, Folder 2)
      - E, 1977 (Box 87, Folder 3)
      - Englund, George, 1977 (Box 87, Folder 4)
      - F, 1977 (Box 87, Folder 5-6)
      - Fields, Shirley Foster, 1977 (Box 87, Folder 7)
      - Foltz, Charles S., 1977 (Box 87, Folder 8)
      - Fonteyn, Margot, 1977 January (Box 87, Folder 9)
      - Fulbright, J. William, 1977 (Box 87, Folder 10)
        Includes correspondence with Elizabeth Fulbright.
      - G, 1977 (Box 87, Folder 11-12)
      - George-Brown, George Alfred Brown, Baron, 1977 November (Box 87, Folder 13)
      - Ginsburg, Ina, 1977 (Box 87, Folder 14)
      - H, 1977 (Box 87, Folder 15)
      - Habib, Philip Charles, 1977-1978 (Box 87, Folder 16)
      - Haley, Alex, 1977 (Box 87, Folder 17)
      - Hall, Robert J., 1977 (Box 87, Folder 18)
        Includes letters from other staff at the Texas Heart Institute.
      - Harriman, W. Averell, 1977 (Box 87, Folder 19)
      - Hartmann, Robert T., 1977 January (Box 88, Folder 1)
      - Helms, Richard, 1977 (Box 88, Folder 2)
      - Herring, Joanne and Robert, 1977 (Box 88, Folder 3-4)
      - Hills, Carla Anderson, 1975-1977 (Box 88, Folder 5)
      - I, 1977 (Box 88, Folder 6)
      - Ikard, Frank Neville and Jayne, 1977 (Box 88, Folder 7)
      - Ingraham, Ronwyn, 1977 (Box 88, Folder 8)
      - Jameson, Frank G. and Eva Gabor, 1977 (Box 88, Folder 9-10)
      - Jaworski, Leon, 1976-1977 (Box 88, Folder 11)
      - Jellicoe, Patricia Christine, Countess of, 1977 (Box 88, Folder 12)
      - Johnson, Lady Bird, 1977 (Box 88, Folder 13)
      - Josephson, Arlette, 1977 (Box 88, Folder 14)
      - K, 1977 (Box 88, Folder 15-17)
      - Kaye, Danny and Sylvia, 1977 (Box 88, Folder 18)
        Includes correspondence with Deena Kaye.
      - Kellogg, Mercedes and Francis L., 1977 (Box 89, Folder 1)
      - Kissinger, Henry, 1974-1977 (Box 89, Folder 2-6)
        Includes correspondence with Nancy Kissinger, and materials related to the ceremony awarding Henry and Nancy with the Order of Homayoun First Class with Grand Cordon and the Order of Haft Paykar, which include the program, texts of speeches, and photocopies of decrees signed by the Shah.
      - Kurze, Brigitte and Theodore, 1977 (Box 89, Folder 7)
      - L, 1977 (Box 89, Folder 8-9)
      - Lance, Bert and LaBelle, 1977 (Box 89, Folder 10)
      - LeBaron, Robert and Peggy, 1977 (Box 89, Folder 11)
      - Lindsay, John V., 1977 (Box 89, Folder 12)
      - Logan, Joshua and Nedda, 1977 (Box 89, Folder 13)
      - Lord, Shirley, 1977 (Box 89, Folder 14)
      - Luce, Clare Boothe, 1977 (Box 89, Folder 15)
      - M, 1977 (Box 90, Folder 1-3)
      - MacArthur, Douglas, 1977 (Box 90, Folder 4)
      - Mansfield, Mike, 1977 (Box 90, Folder 5)
      - Marks, Leonard H., 1977 (Box 90, Folder 6)
      - Marshall, Sylvan M., 1977 (Box 90, Folder 7-10)
        Includes correspondence with Mara Marshall.
      - Mason, James and Clarissa Kaye, 1977 (Box 90, Folder 11)
      - Middendorf, John William, 1977 December (Box 90, Folder 12)
      - Mirza, Humayun, 1977 (Box 90, Folder 13)
        Includes preface for autobiography about Iskander Mirza.
      - Nielsen, Natalie and Mehdi Omana, 1977 (Box 90, Folder 14-15)
      - Neumann, Robert G., 1977-1978 (Box 90, Folder 16)
      - O, 1977 (Box 91, Folder 1-2)
      - P, 1977 (Box 91, Folder 3)
      - Peck, Gregory and Veronique, 1977 (Box 91, Folder 4)
      - R, 1977 (Box 91, Folder 5-7)
      - Rabe, Robert, 1977 (Box 91, Folder 8)
      - Ramsbotham, Peter and Frances, 1977 January (Box 91, Folder 9)
      - Reagan, Ronald, 1977 (Box 91, Folder 10)
        Includes correspondence with Nancy Reagan and a letter from Robert K. Gray.
      - Richardson, Anne and Elliot L., 1977 January-February (Box 91, Folder 11)
      - Robb, Charles S. and Lynda J., 1977 June-July (Box 91, Folder 12)
      - Roberts, B. K. and Mary, 1977 (Box 91, Folder 13)
      - Rockefeller, Nelson A., 1977-1978 (Box 91, Folder 14-15)
      - Rockefeller, Winthrop Paul, 1976-1977 (Box 91, Folder 16)
      - Rogers, William P., 1977-1978 (Box 91, Folder 17)
        Includes correspondence with Adele Rogers and transcript from interview with William Rogers on unrest in Iran.
      - Rumsfeld, Donald, 1977 (Box 91, Folder 18)
      - S, 1977 (Box 92, Folder 1-5)
      - Scheibel, Kenneth, 1977 (Box 92, Folder 6)
      - Schneier, Arthur, 1977 (Box 92, Folder 7)
      - Scott, Hugh, 1977 (Box 92, Folder 8)
      - Scranton, William Warren, 1977 (Box 92, Folder 9)
      - Shawcross, Hartley Shawcross, Baron, 1977 (Box 92, Folder 10)
      - Shore, Dinah, 1977 (Box 92, Folder 11)
      - Shriver, Sargent, 1976-1977 (Box 92, Folder 12)
      - Sisco, Jean Head, 1977 (Box 92, Folder 13)
      - Sittman, William F., 1977 November 19 (Box 92, Folder 14)
      - Smith, Cissy, 1977 (Box 92, Folder 15)
      - Smoak, Marion H., 1976-1977 (Box 92, Folder 16)
      - Strauss, Robert S., 1977 (Box 92, Folder 17)
      - Swearingen, Bonnie and John E., 1977 (Box 93, Folder 1)
      - Symington, James W., 1977 (Box 93, Folder 2)
      - Symington, Stuart, 1977 (Box 93, Folder 3)
      - T, 1977 (Box 93, Folder 4-5)
      - Temple, Shirley, 1977 (Box 93, Folder 6)
      - Tree, Marietta, 1977 (Box 93, Folder 7)
      - Twitchtell, Hamilton A., 1977 (Box 93, Folder 8)
      - Uribe, Mercedes Hanabergh de, 1977 (Box 93, Folder 9)
      - Valley Forge Military Academy, 1977 (Box 93, Folder 10)
        Correspondence with Willard Pearson and Theodore C. Mataxis.
      - Vournas, Anastasia, 1977 September-October (Box 93, Folder 11)
      - W, 1977 (Box 93, Folder 12-14)
      - Warnke, Paul C., 1977 (Box 93, Folder 15)
      - Washburn, C. Langhorne, 1976-1977 (Box 93, Folder 16)
      - Wasserman, Lew and Edie, 1977 (Box 93, Folder 17)
      - Y, 1977 (Box 94, Folder 1)
      - Yatsevitch, Gratian M., 1977 March (Box 94, Folder 2)
      - Z, 1977 (Box 94, Folder 3)
      - Zarb, Frank G., 1976-1977 (Box 94, Folder 4)
    - 1977 press correspondence, 1976-1978
      - A, 1977 (Box 94, Folder 5)
      - Agronsky, Martin and Sharon, 1977 (Box 94, Folder 6)
      - B, 1977 (Box 94, Folder 7)
      - Bartlett, Charles Leffingwell and Martha, 1977 (Box 94, Folder 8)
      - Bayless, Glen, 1977 January-February (Box 94, Folder 9)
      - Beale, Betty, 1977-1978 (Box 94, Folder 10)
        Includes letters from George Graeber.
      - Borchgrave, Arnaud de, 1977 (Box 94, Folder 11)
      - Braun, Jonathan, 1977 (Box 94, Folder 12)
      - Brinkley, David and Susan, 1977 (Box 94, Folder 13)
      - Brokaw, Tom, 1977 (Box 94, Folder 14)
      - C, 1977 (Box 94, Folder 15)
      - Chancellor, John, 1977 (Box 94, Folder 16)
      - Christopher, Rita G., 1977 (Box 94, Folder 17)
      - Christy, Marian, 1977 (Box 94, Folder 18)
      - Clark, Deena, 1977 (Box 95, Folder 1)
      - Cronkite, Walter, 1977 (Box 95, Folder 2)
      - D, 1977 (Box 95, Folder 3)
      - Daniel, Clifton, 1977 May (Box 95, Folder 4)
      - Digges, Sam C., 1977 (Box 95, Folder 5)
      - Dormann, Henry O., 1977-1978 (Box 95, Folder 6-7)
      - Durrell, Richard J., 1977 (Box 95, Folder 8)
      - Epstein, Eleni and Sidney, 1977 (Box 95, Folder 9)
      - Evans, Rowland, 1977 (Box 95, Folder 10)
      - F, 1977 (Box 95, Folder 11)
      - Goodman, Julian, 1977 (Box 95, Folder 12)
      - Graham, Katharine, 1977-1978 (Box 95, Folder 13)
        Includes correspondence about Ghulām Ḥusayn Sāʻidī.
      - Green, Gerald, 1977 (Box 95, Folder 14)
        Includes transcript for interview with Zahedi for Military Electronics Countermeasures magazine, along with preparatory notes.
      - H, 1977 (Box 95, Folder 15)
      - Handy, Delores, 1977 (Box 95, Folder 16)
      - Hartman, David, 1977 (Box 95, Folder 17)
      - K, 1977 (Box 95, Folder 18)
      - Kingsbury-Smith, Joseph, 1977 (Box 95, Folder 19)
      - Leonard, Bill and Kappy, 1977 (Box 96, Folder 1, Box 95, Folder 20)
      - Less, Gunther L., 1977 (Box 96, Folder 2-3)
        Includes September/October issue of Homa: Iran National Air Lines Inflight Magazine, and press release for television epispode "Religions of Iran."
      - Levine, Irving R., 1977 (Box 96, Folder 4)
      - M, 1977 (Box 96, Folder 5)
      - Manley, Joan D., 1977 (Box 96, Folder 6)
      - Margolies-Mezvinsky, Marjorie, 1977 (Box 96, Folder 7)
      - Meaney, Donald V., 1977 (Box 96, Folder 8)
      - Mitchell, Pat, 1977 (Box 96, Folder 9)
      - National Geographic Society, 1977 (Box 96, Folder 10)
      - Newman, Edwin, 1977 January-February (Box 96, Folder 11)
      - Paley, William S., 1977 (Box 96, Folder 12)
      - R, 1977 (Box 96, Folder 13)
      - Rowan, Carl T., 1977 (Box 96, Folder 14)
      - S, 1977 (Box 96, Folder 15)
      - Schlosser, Herbert S., 1977 January-March (Box 96, Folder 16)
      - Scott, Frank, 1977 (Box 96, Folder 17)
      - Stackelberg, Garnett, 1977 (Box 96, Folder 18)
      - Stone, Martin L., 1977 (Box 97, Folder 1)
      - Sulzberger, Arthur Ochs, 1977 (Box 97, Folder 2)
        Includes unsent letter from Zahedi to the New York Times editor in response to Senator Thomas Eagleton's articles on the sale of AWACS planes to Iran.
      - Swinton, Stanley M., 1977 (Box 97, Folder 3)
        Includes copy of proposal from the Associated Press to Pars News Agency and correspondence with Helen Swinton.
      - Thayer, Jack, G., 1977 (Box 97, Folder 4)
      - Thomas, Fred, 1977 November 15 (Box 97, Folder 5)
      - Thomas, Lowell, 1977 (Box 97, Folder 6)
      - V, 1977 (Box 97, Folder 7)
      - Valenti, Jack, 1977 (Box 97, Folder 8)
      - W, 1977 (Box 97, Folder 9)
      - Wald, Richard C., 1977 (Box 97, Folder 10)
      - Wallace, Mike, 1976-1977 (Box 97, Folder 11)
      - Walters, Barbara, 1977 (Box 97, Folder 12-13)
      - Washington Star, 1977 (Box 97, Folder 14)
      - Whedon, Peggy, 1977 (Box 97, Folder 15)
        Includes transcipt from interview with the Shah conducted by Bob Clark and Barbara Walters.
      - Yates, Mary O., 1977 November (Box 97, Folder 16)
      - ZeVan, Barry, 1977 (Box 97, Folder 17)
    - Unfiled correspondence, 1977 (Box 97, Folder 18, Box 98, Folder 1-2)
      Letters addressed to Zahedi and the Shah from Americans and some Iranians, arranged alphabetically by last name. Includes accompanying embassy documents and printed material, Āshūr/Atour: The Assyrian Political, Social, and Cultural Newspaper no. 148 (publication in English, Persian, and Syriac), November 6, 1977 and article submitted to this publication regarding anti-Shah demonstrations at Assyrian rally for the Shah.
    - 1977 state visit files
      - Farah Pahlavi in the United States, 1977 (Box 98, Folder 3-7)
        Includes intinerary, guest lists, logistical correspondence and documents, a poem from Iranians living in New York, program from the Appeal of Conscience Foundation Award, and incoming letters regarding her visit from politicians, journalists, and other people who met with Farah.
      - Letters from Mohammad Reza Pahlavi to Queen Elizabeth and Queen Anne, 1977 November 15 (Box 98, Folder 8)
        Carbon copies.
      - Mohammad Reza and Farah Pahlavi in the United States, 1977 (Box 98, Folder 9-12)
        Includes schedule, drafts of typed letter from Mohammad Reza Pahlavi to Jimmy Carter, Blair House guest list, incoming letters to the Pahlavis, a note from Zahedi to Farah, and invitations for the Pahlavis to White House dinner and for Farah to the Blair House.
      - 1977 November 16, press conference, Blair House, 1977 October-November (Box 98, Folder 13)
        Consists of attendance lists and invitations.
    - 1977 Christmas files
      - Gift lists, 1977 (Box 98, Folder 14-16)
      - Press addresses, 1977 (Box 99, Folder 1)
      - Delivery receipts, 1977 (Box 99, Folder 2-3)
      - Miscellaneous, 1977 (Box 99, Folder 4)
        Includes gift lists, some correspondence, notes, a receipt, and an embassy Christmas card.
      - Gifts and cards received, 1977 (Box 99, Folder 5-6)
    - 1978 White House correspondence
      - Brzezinski, Zbigniew, 1978 (Box 99, Folder 7-8)
      - Clough, Susan, 1978 (Box 99, Folder 9)
      - Hoyt, Mary Finch, 1978 (Box 99, Folder 10)
      - Jordan, Hamilton, 1978 (Box 99, Folder 11)
      - Mondale, Walter F., 1978 (Box 99, Folder 12)
      - Strauss, Robert S., 1978 (Box 99, Folder 13)
      - Watson, Jack H., 1978 December (Box 99, Folder 14)
    - 1978 US State Department correspondence, 1977-1978
      - Atherton, Alfred L., 1978 (Box 99, Folder 15)
      - Benson, Lucy W., 1977-1978 (Box 99, Folder 16)
      - Christopher, Warren, 1978 (Box 99, Folder 17)
      - Conger, Clement E., 1978 (Box 99, Folder 18)
      - Daly, Patrick, 1978 (Box 99, Folder 19)
      - Dobelle, Evan and Kit, 1978 (Box 99, Folder 20)
      - Linowitz, Sol M., 1978 (Box 100, Folder 1)
      - Naas, Charles W., 1978 March (Box 100, Folder 2)
      - Newsom, David D., 1978 (Box 100, Folder 3)
      - Vance, Cyrus R., 1978 (Box 100, Folder 4)
      - Young, Andrew, 1978 January 27 (Box 100, Folder 5)
    - 1978 US Department of Defense correspondence
      - Air Force, 1978 (Box 100, Folder 6)
      - Alexander, Clifford L., Jr., 1978 (Box 100, Folder 7)
      - Army, 1978 (Box 100, Folder 8)
      - Brown, Harold, 1978 (Box 100, Folder 9)
      - Duncan, Charles William, 1978 (Box 100, Folder 10)
      - Huyser, Robert E., 1978 (Box 100, Folder 11)
      - Jones, David C., 1978 (Box 100, Folder 12)
      - Navy, 1978 (Box 100, Folder 13)
      - Siler, Owen Wesley, 1978 (Box 100, Folder 14)
      - Stetson, John C., 1978 (Box 100, Folder 15)
      - Tallman, Kenneth L., 1978 (Box 100, Folder 16)
        Includes letter to Zahedi from the Iranian air force.
      - Tighe, Eugene F., 1978 (Box 100, Folder 17)
      - United States Air Force Academy, 1978 (Box 100, Folder 18)
      - Wilson, Louis H., 1978 (Box 100, Folder 19)
    - 1978 US Government Agencies correspondence
      - Central Intelligence Agency, 1978 (Box 100, Folder 20)
        Includes correspondence with Stansfield Turner.
      - Department of Agriculture, 1978 (Box 100, Folder 21)
        Includes correspondence with Bob Selmer Bergland.
      - Department of Commerce, 1978 (Box 100, Folder 22)
        Includes letter from Juanita M. Kreps.
      - Department of Health, Education and Welfare, 1978 (Box 101, Folder 1)
        Correspondence with Joseph A. Califano, Jr.
      - Department of Housing and Urban Development, 1978 May (Box 101, Folder 2)
        Correspondence with Patricia Harris.
      - Department of the Interior, 1978 January (Box 101, Folder 3)
        Correspondence with Cecil D. Andrus.
      - Department of the Treasury, 1978 (Box 101, Folder 4)
        Includes correspondence with W. Michael Blumenthal.
      - Federal Bureau of Investigation, 1978 (Box 101, Folder 5)
        Correspondence with William H. Webster.
      - Federal Reserve System, 1978 January-February (Box 101, Folder 6)
      - National Security Council, 1978 (Box 101, Folder 7)
    - 1978 Supreme Court correspondence
      - Burger, Warren E., 1978 (Box 101, Folder 8)
      - Powell, Lewis F., 1978 (Box 101, Folder 9)
      - Rehnquist, William H., 1978 January-February (Box 101, Folder 10)
      - Stewart, Potter, 1978 (Box 101, Folder 11)
      - White, Byron R., 1978 July 6-7 (Box 101, Folder 12)
    - 1978 US Senate correspondence, 1977-1978
      - Administrative, 1978 (Box 101, Folder 13)
      - Baker, Howard H., Jr., 1978 November-December (Box 101, Folder 14)
      - Bayh, Birch, 1978 (Box 101, Folder 15-16)
      - Bentsen, Lloyd, 1978 December 21-23 (Box 101, Folder 17)
      - Brooke, Edward W., 1978 (Box 101, Folder 18)
      - Bumpers, Dale, 1978 (Box 101, Folder 19)
      - Byrd, Harry F., Jr., 1977 (Box 101, Folder 20)
      - Byrd, Robert C., 1977-1978 (Box 101, Folder 21)
      - Church, Frank, 1977-1978 (Box 101, Folder 22)
      - Dole, Robert J., 1978 (Box 101, Folder 23)
      - Domenici, Pete, 1978 (Box 101, Folder 24)
      - Goldwater, Barry M., 1978 (Box 101, Folder 25)
      - Hatfield, Mark O., 1978 (Box 101, Folder 26)
      - Hatfield, Paul Gerhart, 1978 June 27-29 (Box 102, Folder 1)
      - Jackson, Henry M., 1977-1978 (Box 102, Folder 2)
      - Javits, Jacob K., 1978 (Box 102, Folder 3)
        Includes copy of letter from the Embassy of Pakistan to Javitz regarding Zulfikar Ali Bhutto's death sentence.
      - Kennedy, Edward M., 1978 (Box 102, Folder 4)
      - Long, Russell B., 1978 (Box 102, Folder 5)
      - Magnuson, Warren G., 1978 (Box 102, Folder 6)
      - Mathias, Charles McC., 1977-1978 (Box 102, Folder 7)
      - McGovern, George S., 1978 (Box 102, Folder 8)
      - Nunn, Sam, 1978 December 12-18 (Box 102, Folder 9)
      - Pell, Claiborne, 1978 (Box 102, Folder 10)
      - Percy, Charles H., 1978 (Box 102, Folder 11)
      - Ribicoff, Abraham, 1978 (Box 102, Folder 12-13)
      - Schweiker, Richard S., 1978 (Box 102, Folder 14)
      - Sparkman, John, 1978 (Box 102, Folder 15)
      - Stennis, John C., 1978 December 14-18 (Box 102, Folder 16)
      - Stevenson, Adlai E., III, 1978 (Box 102, Folder 17)
      - Stone, Richard, 1978 (Box 102, Folder 18)
      - Talmadge, Herman E., 1978 June 23-28 (Box 103, Folder 1)
      - Thurmond, Strom, 1978 December 12-14 (Box 103, Folder 2)
      - Tower, John G., 1978 (Box 103, Folder 3)
    - 1978 US House of Representatives correspondence, 1977-1978
      - Anderson, Glenn M., 1978 September (Box 103, Folder 4)
        Includes photocopy of Anderson's statement on Iran to Congress as printed in the Congressional Record.
      - Bingham, Jonathan B., 1977-1978 (Box 103, Folder 5)
      - Boggs, Lindy, 1978 (Box 103, Folder 6)
      - Brademas, John, 1977-1978 (Box 103, Folder 7)
      - Brooks, Jack, 1978 December 12-15 (Box 103, Folder 8)
      - Cederberg, Elford A., 1978 (Box 103, Folder 9)
      - Cohen, William S., 1978 (Box 103, Folder 10)
      - Fascell, Dante B., 1978 February 23 (Box 103, Folder 11)
      - Findley, Paul, 1978 (Box 103, Folder 12)
      - Glickman, Dan, 1978 (Box 103, Folder 13)
      - Hamilton, Lee, 1978 June-July (Box 103, Folder 14)
      - Heftel, Cecil, 1978 (Box 103, Folder 15)
      - Holt, Marjorie, 1978 (Box 103, Folder 16)
      - Jenrette, John W., 1978 (Box 103, Folder 17)
      - Lehman, William, 1978 December 13-14 (Box 103, Folder 18)
      - Mahon, George Herman, 1977-1978 (Box 103, Folder 19)
      - Mann, James R., 1978 April 18-21 (Box 103, Folder 20)
      - McDonald, Lawrence Patton, 1978 (Box 103, Folder 21)
      - Meyner, Helen S., 1977-1978 (Box 103, Folder 22)
      - Montgomery, G. V., 1978 (Box 103, Folder 23)